Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
Ron Kolm Papers
1970-2018
Fales Library and Special Collections
Kolm, Ron
MSS.079
67 Linear Feet in 65 boxes and flat file folders
2 audiocassettes
12 dvd-r disks
7 sound discs (cd)
Ron Kolm is a writer, editor, artist, promoter, has been the de facto archivist and an enduring member of the Soho and East Village arts scene from the mid-1970s to the present day. During this period, he has been involved with several independent bookstores, small magazines, performance spaces, and the outsider art scene. Kolm continues to be heavily involved in avant garde work, serving as a main organizer of The Unbearables, a loosely organized group of downtown writers and artists, perhaps best known for their protests against mainstream notions of "good" or "bad" literature and art. Through his work, Kolm has collected over 6000 items that comprise this collection. Items include: signed first editions and chapbooks by authors such as Kathy Acker, Lynne Tillman, Gary Indiana, Spalding Gray, Patrick McGrath, Harry Mathews, Hal Sirowitz, Max Blagg, Janice Eidus, Constance DeJong, David Wojnarowicz, among many others; as well as: complete runs of Between C and D, Red Tape, Zone, The Portable Lower East Side, Beat, Vox, and The National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side, among others.
Custodial History
The Ron Kolm Papers were acquired via purchase from Mr. Kolm in December of 1996. The collection was sorted by Marvin J. Taylor once it arrived at NYU. Multiple accretions have also been added to the collection since the original donation.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers.
Biographical Note
Ron Kolm, poet, writer, editor, artist, promoter, and long-time member of the downtown scene served as the de facto archivist of the Soho and East Village arts scene beginning in the mid-1970s. Through his work in various independent bookstores and his active involvement in small magazines, performance spaces, and the outsider art scene, Ron Kolm, amassed this collection. Ron's poem "Suburban Ambush" was selected by Robert Siegle as the title for his book, Suburban Ambush: Downtown Writing and the Fiction of Insurgency (Johns Hopkins University Press, 1989). Kolm continues to be heavily involved in avant garde work, serving as a main organizer of The Unbearables, a loosely organized group of downtown writers and artists, perhaps best known for their protests against the poetry of The New Yorker and other acts of "poetic terrorism" intended to point out how society constructs the notions of "good" or "bad" literature and art.
Scope and Contents
The Ron Kolm Papers consists of material created and collected by Kolm from 1970 up to the present, broadly documenting artists and writers in this period of the Downtown Scene. The collection comprises his personal correspondence with members of that scene; manuscripts in various stages; photographs; audio recordings; video recordings; clippings files from newspapers and magazines; posters; original art; production files for his small press, Low Tech Press; and materials about the various events and publications of The Unbearables. He also has collected books, serials, zines, and other ephemera relating to the scene of which he is considered an integral part. The collection also includes inscribed copies of books; signed first editions and chapbooks by authors such as Kathy Acker, Lynne Tillman, Gary Indiana, Walter Abish, Spaulding Gray, Patrick McGrath, Harry Mathews, Hal Sirowitz, Max Blagg, Janice Eidus, Constance DeJong, David Wojnarowicz, Jeffrey Cyphers Wright; and complete runs of significant literary magazines of the 1980-1990s scene, including Between C and D, Appearances, Red Tape, Benzene, Zone, The Portable Lower East Side, Beat, Vox, Semi(o)texte, Peau Sensible, Raw, and The National Poetry Magazine of the Lower East Side. Assembly magazines, zines, posters, flyers, catalogues of exhibitions, and announcements for readings provide a sense of the downtown arts scene of the Soho and East Village during its artistic height. The collection is also rich in materials relating to non-literary artists, and includes some writings by those artists, including David Wojnarowicz, Keith Haring, Art Spiegelman, and others.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject/author heading.
The files are grouped into 14 subject and material type oriented series. Accretions have been added at the end. Accretions from 2015, 2016, 2018, and 2019 have not been arranged by an archivist; these materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Series List
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Manuscripts
Series III: The Unbearables
Series IV: Subject Files
Series V: Photographs
Series VI: Announcements
Series VII: Sound Recordings
Series VIII: Original Art
Series IX: Ephemera
Series X: Low Tech Press
Series XI: Posters
Series XII: Catalogs
Series XIII: Calendars [note: all calendars are oversize]
Series XIV: Periodicals
Oversize - Series II: Manuscripts
Oversize - Series III: The Unbearables
Oversize - Series IV: Subject Files
Oversize - Series V: Photographs
Oversize - Series VIII: Original Art
Oversize - Series X: Low Tech Press
Oversize - Series XII: Catalogs
Accretions 1995-1999 - Series I: Correspondence
Accretions 1995-1999 - Series II: Manuscripts
Accretions 1995-1999 - Series IV: Subject Files
Accretions 1995-1999 - Series V: Photographs
Accretions 1995-1999 - Series VI: Announcements
Accretions 1995-1999 - Series VIII: Original Art
Accretions 1995-1999 - Series IX: Ephemera
Accretions 1995-1999 - Series XI: Posters
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series I: Correspondence
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series II: Manuscripts
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series III: The Unbearables
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series IV: Subject Files
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series V: Photographs
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series VI: Announcements
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series VII: Sound Recordings
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series VIII: Original Art
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series IX: Ephemera
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series XI: Posters
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series XII: Catalogs
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series XIII: Calendars
Accretions 2001-2002 - Series XIV: Periodicals
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series I: Correspondence
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series II: Manuscripts
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series III: The Unbearables
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series IV:Subject Files
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series V: Photographs
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series VI: Announcements
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series VII: Sound Recordings
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series VIII: Original Art
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series IX: Ephemera
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series XI: Posters
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series XII: Catalogs
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series XIII: Calendars
Accretions 2002-2003 - Series XIV: Periodicals
Accretions 2015-2016
Accretions 2018
Accretions 2019
Separated Material
Selected printed materials have been removed and individually catalogued in the Downtown Periodicals Collection. Records for these items can be retrieved through Bobcat.
Following is a list of the printed materials that were removed from the Accretions 2002-2003 portion of the collection and moved into the Downtown Periodicals Collection.
American Book Review: 23.5-24.4 July/August 2002-May/June 2003.
The Brooklyn Rail (August-September 2002); (Winter 2003); (April-May 2003).
Gargoyle 45 (2002).
Long Shot 25 (2002) 20th Anniversary Edition, "On 9/11", 2002.
NY Arts 7.11 (November 2002).
Poetry Project Newsletter 187-195, 2001-2003.
Rain Taxi Review of Books 6.3-7.1; 7.3, 2001-2002.
Tamarind (May 1998).
World War 3 Illustrated 33 (2002).
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Ron Kolm Papers were acquired via purchase from Ron Kolm in December of 1996.
Clippings (information artifacts); Authors, American -- 20th century.; Artists and community -- United States; Artists' writings; Correspondence.; New York (N.Y.).; Printed ephemera.; Sound recordings.; Poetry.; Scripts (documents); Small presses -- New York (State) -- New York.; Manuscripts for publication.; Posters.; Video recordings.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Literature, Experimental.; Poets, American -- 20th century.; Downtown writers.; Photographs.; Drawings; Spiegelman, Art; Wojnarowicz, David; Unbearables (Literary group); Gray, Spalding, 1941-2004; Mathews, Harry, 1930-; Tillman, Lynne; Sirowitz, Hal; McGrath, Patrick, 1950-; Indiana, Gary; Eidus, Janice; Blagg, Max; Haring, Keith; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Wright, Jeffery C. (Jeffrey Cyphers)
- Series I: Correspondence, 14494
  Scope and Content
  This series consists of correspondence between Ron Kolm and a wide range of downtown artists and writers.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by correspondent and chronologically within each folder.
  - Acheson, Alice, undated; 14856 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ackerman, Pat, undated; 14855 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ahern, Tom, undated; 14854 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alexander, Lynn, undated; 14853 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alfaro, Rosanna, undated; 14852 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Roberta, undated; 14851 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Amedeo, Joann, undated; 14850 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aminoff, Judith, undated; 14849 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Holy, undated; 14848 (Box 1, Folder 8A)
  - Andrucyk, Inez, undated; 14847 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anthony, Bill, undated; 14846 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anxiety, Little Annie, undated; 14845 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arias, Vicki, undated; 14844 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Armijo, Richard, undated; 14843 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Armleder, John, undated; 14842 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Armstrong, Alison, undated; 14841 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Aycock, Shirley, undated; 14840 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Azon, Gary, undated; 14839 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baldi, Malaga, undated; 14838 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ballard, Tony, undated; 14837 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Barkin, George, undated; 14836 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Barry, Judith, undated; 14835 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Basely-Nylon, Judy, undated; 14834 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Basinski, Michael, undated; 14833 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bealy, Allan, undated; 14832 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bear, Liza, undated; 14831 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Belden, Kathryn, undated; 14830 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Benderson, Bruce, undated; 14829 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Benedict, Kitty, undated; 14828 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bernstein, Charles, undated; 14827 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bertrand, Kate, undated; 14826 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bey, Hakim, undated; 14825 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Blagg, Max, undated; 14824 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Blaushild, Lisa, undated; 14823 (Box 1, Folder 32A)
  - Bloom, Jodi, undated; 14822 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Blowdryer, Jennifer, undated; 14821 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Boccio, Karen, undated; 14820 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Boss, Laura, undated; 14819 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bowery, Zagreus, undated; 14818 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Brandt, Pamela, undated; 14817 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Brendan-Brown, Sean, undated; 14816 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bridges, Les, undated; 14815 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Brown, Charlotte, undated; 14814 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Brown, Ken, undated; 14813 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Brownstein, Michael, undated; 14812 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Buczak, Brian, undated; 14811 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Bunell, Elizabeth, undated; 14810 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Bush, Catherine, undated; 14809 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Calhoun, Harry, undated; 14808 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cannon, Steve, undated; 14807 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Cantsin, Monty, undated; 14806 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Cardoni, Ed, undated; 14805 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Carter, Ellen, undated; 14804 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Carter, Michael, undated; 14803 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Castleman, David, undated; 14802 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Chiappetta, Joe, undated; 14801 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Cherches, Peter, undated; 14800 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Church, Tom, undated; 14799 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Clemons, Brian, undated; 14798 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Codrescu, Andrei, undated; 14797 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Cohen, Mo, undated; 14796 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Colby, Todd, undated; 14795 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Cole, David, undated; 14794 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Collins & Milazzo, undated; 14793 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Conlon, Daniel, undated; 14792 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Conlon, Eddie, undated; 14791 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Coutreau, Bob, undated; 14790 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Crawford, Lynn, undated; 14789 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Criton, Paul, undated; 14788 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Compton, Ken, undated; 14787 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Curcio, Robert, undated; 14786 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Daitch, Susan, undated; 14785 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Dalachinsky, Steve, undated; 14784 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Davis, Bob, undated; 14783 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Denson, Janie, undated; 14782 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - D'Erasmo, Stacey, undated; 14781 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Deyab, Larry, undated; 14780 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - DiMaggio, Ken, undated; 14779 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Djikstra, undated; 14778 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Dlugos, Tim, undated; 14777 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Doering, Steven, undated; 14776 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Dougherty, Lynn, undated; 14775 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Duhamel, Denise, undated; 14774 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Duvanel, Fonda, undated; 14773 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Dye, Bru, undated; 14772 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Eidus, Janice, undated; 14771 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Elmslie, Kenward, undated; 14770 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Estep, Maggie, undated; 14769 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Evans, Tom, undated; 14768 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Fairon, Laurent, undated; 14767 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Feldman, Anita, undated; 14766 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Fillingham, Patricia, undated; 14765 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Finberg, Bonny, undated; 14764 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Fish, Cheryl, undated; 14763 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Fishberg, Lawrence, undated; 14762 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Fisher, Dennis, undated; 14761 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Fleming, Jim, undated; 14760 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Forbes, David, undated; 14759 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Fortune, Merry, undated; 14758 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Fox, S. K. or Kate, undated; 14757 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Fredericks, Karen, undated; 14756 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Freels, Brandon, undated; 14755 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Fried, Steve, undated; 14754 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Friedman, Michael, undated; 14753 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Gagnon, Ron, undated; 14752 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Galassi, Jonathan, undated; 14751 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Gekiere, Madeleine, undated; 14750 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - George, Michael, undated; 14749 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Gillan, Maria, undated; 14748 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Gilman, S.E, undated; 14747 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, undated; 14746 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Glasheen, Kevin, undated; 14745 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Goad, Jim, undated; 14744 (Box 1, Folder 110A)
  - Goldbeck, Sedrick, undated; 14743 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Golden, Mike, undated; 14742 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Gordon, Kirpal, undated; 14741 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Gosciak, Josh, undated; 14740 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Graham, James, undated; 14739 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Graham, Nan, undated; 14738 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Griffin, George, undated; 14737 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Groffsky, Maxine, undated; 14736 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Gunderson, Joanna, undated; 14735 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Hageman, Leita, undated; 14734 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Hallgren, Will, undated; 14733 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Halpern, Daniel, undated; 14732 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Hamill, Janet, undated; 14731 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Hamill, Tom, undated; 14730 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Head, Glenn, undated; 14729 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Heller, Jay, undated; 14728 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Hershon, Robert, undated; 14727 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Herzog, Ron, undated; 14726 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Himmelstein, Shelley, undated; 14725 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Holland, Barbara, undated; 14724 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Holman, Bob, undated; 14723 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Hoshino, Stacy, undated; 14722 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Howard, Gerald, undated; 14721 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Howell, Tracy, undated; 14720 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Hudspith, Vicki, undated; 14719 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Huncke, Herbert, undated; 14718 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Jankowski, Matty, undated; 14717 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Jerome, Judson, undated; 14716 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Jets, Ruby, undated; 14715 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Johnson, Charles, undated; 14714 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Johnson, Paul, undated; 14713 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Jolis, Alan, undated; 14712 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Jordan, Ken, undated; 14711 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Joseph, Jennifer, undated; 14710 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Kabat, Jennifer, undated; 14709 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Kane, Steven, undated; 14708 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Kasper, Michael, undated; 14707 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Kaufman, Alan, undated; 14706 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Kaz, undated; 14705 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Kennison, Jon, undated; 14704 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Kessler, Lee, undated; 14703 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Kidde, Katharine, undated; 14702 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Kiernan, Kathy, undated; 14701 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - King, J.D, undated; 14700 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Kitchen, Dennis, undated; 14699 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Kold, Buddy, undated; 14698 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated; 14697 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Kraus, Chris, undated; 14696 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Kraut, Shelley, undated; 14695 (Box 1, Folder 158A)
  - Kronenberg, Mindy, undated; 14694 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Kruth, John, undated; 14693 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated; 14692 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - LaBombarda, Michael, undated; 14691 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Lamar, Jill, undated; 14690 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Lambert, Nancy, undated; 14689 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Lance, Jeanne, undated; 14688 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Landers, Jennifer, undated; 14687 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Lapides, Beth, undated; 14686 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Laurence, Alexander, undated; 14685 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Leary, Mary, undated; 14684 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Legan, Mark, undated; 14683 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Leggiere, Phil, undated; 14682 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Lev, Donald, undated; 14681 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Lew, Walter, undated; 14680 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Lewis, Joel, undated; 14679 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Lichele, Edward, undated; 14678 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Lida, David, undated; 14677 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Lindenberg, Hal, undated; 14676 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Lindquist, Ona, undated; 14675 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Litzsky, Tsaurah, undated; 14674 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Liu, Perry, undated; 14673 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Lobaco, Gina, undated; 14672 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Lopatin, Judy, undated; 14671 (Box 1, Folder 181A)
  - Ludwig, Bob, undated; 14670 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Maher, Arlene, undated; 14669 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Mandl, Dave, undated; 14668 (Box 1, Folder 183A)
  - Mansion, Gracie, undated; 14667 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Marinaro, Pat, undated; 14666 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Marshall, Richard, undated; 14665 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Martin, John, undated; 14664 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Masters, Greg, undated; 14663 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mathews, Harry, undated; 14662 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mattsson, J. Michael, undated; 14661 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Maury, Joe, undated; 14660 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Max, Daniel, undated; 14659 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Maxwell, Noemie, undated; 14658 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Maynard, Joe, undated; 14657 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mazzucchelli, David, undated; 14656 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - MacDonnell, Allen, undated; 14655 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mc Allister, Marian, undated; 14654 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mc Caffrey, Larry, undated; 14653 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mc Cain, Gillian, undated; 14652 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mc Cormick, Carlo, undated; 14651 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mc Donnell, Evelyn, undated; 14650 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mc Duffie, Phillip, undated; 14649 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mc Glynn, Bob, undated; 14648 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mc Gonigle, Tom, undated; 14647 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mc Gowran, Siobhan, undated; 14646 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Mc Pherson, Bruce, undated; 14645 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mesmer, Sharon, undated; 14644 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Mikolowski, Ken, undated; 14643 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Miller, John, undated; 14642 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Miller, Robert, undated; 14641 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Millin, Laura, undated; 14640 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Mind Over Matter Edith, undated; 14639 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Moisan, Jim, undated; 14638 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Molinaro, Ursule, undated; 14637 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Moore, Steven, undated; 14636 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Morse, Elizabeth, undated; 14635 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Mouly, Francoise, undated; 14634 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Munro, Donna, undated; 14633 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Murphy, Tricia, undated; 14632 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Myles, Eileen, undated; 14631 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Nechvatal, Joseph, undated; 14630 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Nersesian, Arthur, undated; 14629 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Nesci, John, undated; 14628 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Nestor, Jack, undated; 14627 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Nettlebeck, F.A, undated; 14626 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Nicosia, Gerry, undated; 14625 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Niditch, B.Z, undated; 14624 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Norton, Margot, undated; 14623 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Nostrand, Jennifer, undated; 14622 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Nurkse, Dennis, undated; 14621 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Obssuth, Karen, undated; 14620 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Ochiishi, undated; 14619 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - O'Keefe, Steve, undated; 14618 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Olinder, Laurie, undated; 14617 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Pieto, Rick, undated; 14616 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Pintonelli, Deborah, undated; 14615 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Olsen, Lance, undated; 14614 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Osterman, Susan, undated; 14613 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Owen, Maureen, undated; 14612 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Packer, Eve, undated; 14611 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Padua, Jose, undated; 14610 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Palaia, Franc, undated; 14609 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Passaro, Vince, undated; 14608 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Peabody, Richard, undated; 14607 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Pearlman, Allan, undated; 14606 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Peditte, Chris, undated; 14605 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Penzner, Marina, undated; 14604 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Peyser, Carolyn, undated; 14603 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Peyster, Steven, undated; 14602 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Phipps, Wanda, undated; 14601 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Plantenga, Bart, undated; 14600 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Plumlee, Steven, undated; 14599 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Polonoff, David, undated; 14598 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Pop, Iggy, undated; 14597 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Potash, Chris, undated; 14596 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Preuss, R.S, undated; 14595 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Rabinowitz, Jacob, undated; 14594 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Rage, J.D, undated; 14593 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Rapaport, Jill, undated; 14592 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Ratajczak, Donna, undated; 14591 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Rattray, David, undated; 14590 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Raveson, Art, undated; 14589 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Reid, undated; 14588 (Box 2, Folder 80)